{
  "aggregations": {
    "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "ab4b1482cb2ba3f1ee7fd9201c8a1fad": {
              "answer": "War",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
              "answer": "ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Once more into the breach my friends. It's a hard day.  It's a red day. Let's rejoice!"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "a181a603769c1f98ad927e7367c7aa51": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "",
        "question": "all",
        "answer": "all"
      },
      "count": 13,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "6839d672141795d0959700017e3cdec4": {
              "answer": "Cats",
              "count": 1
            },
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 5
            },
            "8cec7d6c891fc360bfd61e14b8512896": {
              "answer": "Justice",
              "count": 2
            },
            "9e5a1ebfc5b29bbccdbfdde4c0dc621e": {
              "answer": "Naptime",
              "count": 1
            },
            "ab4b1482cb2ba3f1ee7fd9201c8a1fad": {
              "answer": "War",
              "count": 4
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "86d88d9e4e39979f13b822d1643a95f4": {
              "answer": "ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸",
              "count": 1
            },
            "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜’",
              "count": 1
            },
            "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜³",
              "count": 6
            },
            "d6707e4336e1d5b88c06c60f1f2fe383": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜¸",
              "count": 2
            },
            "e36f865a311bb2bcec6a270ab3083028": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜ƒ",
              "count": 1
            },
            "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜ª",
              "count": 2
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Hihi",
            "Yoyo",
            "Lala",
            "Dada",
            "A new one!",
            "Congrats on your victory, Mrs. President!",
            "So glad it's over...",
            "This was the best election season ever! Can we just start campaigning for 2020 now?",
            "Boring. I want a nap.",
            "Election?  Was there an election?  Who's gonna be the president?  I hope it's not me?!",
            "Cats do not receive enough respect.  Not even close!",
            "Once more into the breach my friends. It's a hard day.  It's a red day. Let's rejoice!",
            "Let's get our criminal justice system in line with any coherent conception of justice."
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "ðŸ˜’"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "9e5a1ebfc5b29bbccdbfdde4c0dc621e": {
              "answer": "Naptime",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "bf1f01da0bfa69d071d64823cefbdf4c": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜’",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Boring. I want a nap."
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "ðŸ˜³"
      },
      "count": 6,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 3
            },
            "8cec7d6c891fc360bfd61e14b8512896": {
              "answer": "Justice",
              "count": 1
            },
            "ab4b1482cb2ba3f1ee7fd9201c8a1fad": {
              "answer": "War",
              "count": 2
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "d1bccc85fc14440d4201e4fa2a7a88a2": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜³",
              "count": 6
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Hihi",
            "Lala",
            "Dada",
            "Congrats on your victory, Mrs. President!",
            "So glad it's over...",
            "Election?  Was there an election?  Who's gonna be the president?  I hope it's not me?!"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "d6707e4336e1d5b88c06c60f1f2fe383": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "ðŸ˜¸"
      },
      "count": 2,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "6839d672141795d0959700017e3cdec4": {
              "answer": "Cats",
              "count": 1
            },
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "d6707e4336e1d5b88c06c60f1f2fe383": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜¸",
              "count": 2
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "Yoyo",
            "Cats do not receive enough respect.  Not even close!"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "e36f865a311bb2bcec6a270ab3083028": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "ðŸ˜ƒ"
      },
      "count": 1,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "ab4b1482cb2ba3f1ee7fd9201c8a1fad": {
              "answer": "War",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "e36f865a311bb2bcec6a270ab3083028": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜ƒ",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "This was the best election season ever! Can we just start campaigning for 2020 now?"
          ]
        }
      }
    },
    "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
      "group": {
        "question_id": "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59",
        "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
        "answer": "ðŸ˜ª"
      },
      "count": 2,
      "mc": {
        "80bd7b99-edc6-435d-9585-8a6014cea52e": {
          "question": "What should the new president focus on first?",
          "answers": {
            "8afc1f2760cfc2d63b8f0e9ddb1b6f39": {
              "answer": "Economy",
              "count": 1
            },
            "8cec7d6c891fc360bfd61e14b8512896": {
              "answer": "Justice",
              "count": 1
            }
          }
        },
        "d21eda82-8000-4e5d-9506-3a41907b6b59": {
          "question": "How do you feel about the incumbent?",
          "answers": {
            "fd212198c64a6510ea26c2c6c14228ba": {
              "answer": "ðŸ˜ª",
              "count": 2
            }
          }
        }
      },
      "text": {
        "d452b94d-e650-41c6-80af-c56091315c90": {
          "question": "What do you want to say?",
          "answers": [
            "A new one!",
            "Let's get our criminal justice system in line with any coherent conception of justice."
          ]
        }
      }
    }
  }
}
